Before anything else,
allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Subaru Natsuki.
I'm an indestructible
vagabond who also happens
to be a complete idiot.
I'm a real ignoramus.
Despite that, I hope we
get along swimmingly.
[groans]
OK.
We already know
all that, don't we?
Certainly far too
late for introductions.
Huh?
So then what you're saying is
that I've known the two of you
for over a year now already,
but that I've somehow
managed to forget?
But, I mean, yeah,
my hand definitely
didn't look like this when
I left the convenience store,
that's for sure.
[EMILIA] You truly
don't remember anything?
This tower or what
happened in Priestella?
Even about us?
I, uh--
yeah,
that sounds right.
But, hey, come on!
I can see how this
could be upsetting,
but let's just stop and think.
As far as I know, people who
have temporary memory loss
usually tend to revert
to a particular moment.
In the movies, they usually
remember within two hours,
then they're totally
back to normal.
So there's no need
to worry too much, OK?
Sorry, I don't quite
understand what that means.
Oh.
No?
But, at the very least,
I know you're still Subaru,
and that puts me at ease.
Hey!
There.
All cheered up.
Things are far worse for you
than me at the moment,
so I shouldn't be making
such unhappy faces.
I would never have
expected someone so cute
to be so incredibly gallant.
Now, you, Beatrice.
Oh, I can't believe
I have to do this.
[groans]
As per usual, you are such
a troublesome contractor,
I suppose.
[SUBARU]
Contractor?
[sighs]
This utterly
burdensome situation
had better not happen again,
or I will lose
my patience with you.
You understand, I suppose?
[soft chuckle]
I am the one and only
Subaru Natsuki!
I don't have any
idea what's going on,
but I think I'm probably
your friend at least.
I know this is pretty
shameless, but I need a favor.
I want you both to tell
me what your names are.
Oh.
Well, my name is Emilia.
Only Emilia.
And Betty is
the great spirit Beatrice.
You are contracted
to Betty, I suppose.
We meet again, Subaru.
Hmm!
[theme music]
♪ ♪
What kind of stupid
joke is this, Barusu?
Ram.
Wait, Barusu?
It's like you turned my name
into a destruction spell.
Then you're
the older sister of the girl
who was sleeping on the bed?
I know that you've been trying
to help wake your sister up.
Sorry about the bad timing.
But still, to be
honest with you,
I'm kinda at my limit.
Can you save any
gripes you have with me
for when I have my memories?
When you talk like that,
it's hard to believe you've
even lost them to begin with.
You're the same old Barusu.
Hiya, Master.
I'm Shaula, AKA
your most beloved pupil.
And I'm also Keeper
of the Pleiades Watchtower.
Uh, did you say "Master"?
You talking about me?
I swear.
Wow, what a guy.
You must really love
being a problem, huh?
And who are you with
that uncomfortable,
sickly sweet look
on your face?
[MEILI]
I'm Meili.
I'm not sure if when
you lost your memories,
you also lost
your knack for sewing,
but if not,
I'd really love it
if you made me
another stuffed toy.
Oh, you know
my best hidden talent?
Then we must be super friendly.
You must be in a little
sister role, like Beatrice.
Actually, that girl is
an assassin who tried to kill
both you and Betty, I suppose.
[SUBARU]
That's a joke, right?
[giggles]
So there's Ram, Shaula, Meili,
and if we're moving on
with the introductions, then--
Just call me Anastasia
for the time being.
My friend, I think he needs
a little time right now.
Is that all right?
[SUBARU]
Yeah, I guess so.
This did happen out of nowhere,
so it must have been a shock.
I suspect that's not
all there is to it,
given his current situation.
But if it hadn't been
for your shocking confession,
let's just say I would have had
a shocking confession of my own
to make.
Huh?
Well, then, I'll get
started on the preparations
for breakfast.
Miss Emilia, may I send
Barusu to fetch some water?
Huh?
But his memory is still vague,
and he must be overwhelmed.
Maybe we should let
him rest for now.
It's all good.
My body's still fine.
I can handle
a little water run.
Yeah, Emilia?
[sighs]
You seem awfully tired.
Well, can you
really blame me?
Plus, I was never the type
to be so considerate of others.
Enough.
Drop this
ridiculous charade, Barusu.
[SUBARU sighs]
I brought you away
from the others.
Now, don't make a woman
embarrass herself, you lecher.
Now I'm a lecher?
This is just another
stupid whim of yours, right?
I understand that Miss
Emilia can't keep a secret,
but you can at least tell
me what you're plotting
now that we're in private.
Uh, sorry to disappoint you,
but this isn't a plot or an act
or a bad joke or anything.
Stubborn, though bearing
too much of the burden alone
is nothing new for you.
[SUBARU]
Look, I told you--
Stop playing
and tell me everything.
Your secret will
be safe with me.
As enticing as it sounds
to have a little secret
between just the two of us--
[groans]
Hey, what the hell was
that for all of a sudden?
[RAM]
Tell me.
I have some ideas as to what
I'll do if you keep this up.
Wow, you really
haven't been listening.
Like I said,
I'm not lying! I--
Tell me everything right now!
Tell me everything.
I--
[RAM]
I'm begging you.
Tell me everything.
But, Ram.
[RAM]
Please.
If even you forget, then I--
and Rem.
Sorry.
[SHAULA]
Hey, Master!
We're starting to run
out of dried meat!
[SUBARU]
Gotcha.
I'm on it.
You'll only make Miss
Emilia and the others worry.
Don't speak of what
just happened.
I apologize about before.
Is now a good time to talk?
Sure.
And I'm sorry
for the shock, too.
Uh, I'll just listen.
I am Julius Juukulius.
Miss Anastasia's--
this lady's first knight.
You and I are
friends, basically.
Oh, yeah?
Nice to know ya.
But why didn't you
sound very sure of that?
I don't think that
you need to worry.
Everyone knows you
and Julius are really
good friends, after all.
Aren't they?
Yeah, they are.
Although Mr. Knight
here looks like
he has something on his mind.
Anything you wanted to tell us?
[RAM] Then is it about Miss
Anastasia's unusual behavior
since this morning?
Exactly that, Miss Ram.
Though I hate to simply tack
it on to Subaru's predicament.
I don't want to just keep
piling on to the
confusion either,
but I'll believe in the bond
we formed fighting
through the dunes together
and tell the full truth.
Well, that's a rather
concerning declaration.
[ANASTASIA] You two
really have the ideal bond.
It's so heartwarming
to witness.
I had hoped to one day
build the same kind
of special
relationship with Ana.
You talk about Miss Anastasia
like she's a different person.
So it's true that you're--
Uh--
Yes, the consciousness
residing in this body
is not hers.
[munches]
She's currently sleeping
deeply inside here.
I'm standing
in for her temporarily.
You may call me Echidna.
Echidna?
[ECHIDNA] Natsuki had
the same reaction.
I suppose that name brings
about certain feelings.
But please know that I'm not
the Echidna you all know.
Oh, sorry if
my reaction was hurtful.
I think it's safe
to say both Subaru
and I were pretty badly
tormented in the past
by someone named Echidna.
So we just happened
to meet someone
else named Echidna, huh?
That other one sure seemed
to have made a mess of things.
She did.
Echidna was a lot of trouble.
We should let her know
if we ever meet again.
I hope that you will.
And given how much she's
managed to harm my reputation,
please speak for me as well.
But the whole reason you
guys all came to this tower
was to help people, right?
So why--
As soon as we
reached the tower
and started making our way up,
the few memories
you had suddenly vanished,
and we learned
Anastasia's consciousness
sleeps in the void.
So straight up not
having a good time.
Um, you know, hey, wallowing
forever won't get us anywhere.
Emilia?
All of us carry the hopes of so
many people on our shoulders.
We have to forge on.
Giving up's not an option.
Someone special taught me that.
Everything Emilia
said is spot on.
I apologize for screwing things
up by losing all my memories,
but our perspective
makes a difference.
Maybe while I'm stuck
in this sorry state,
I can at least come up
with some interesting ideas
that aren't bound
by the rules of this world.
We'll turn this crisis
into our chance!
That certainly is
an optimistic outlook,
to say the very least.
But it's very Subaru,
I suppose.
[EMILIA]
Thank you, Subaru.
I really am so glad you're
still Subaru after all.
Good grief.
Regardless of your memories,
your bravery and reckless
refusal to adhere to a black
and white way of thinking
never change.
But still, I'd like to know
what led you to lose
your memories like that.
The thing is,
I seriously don't
have a clue myself either.
Emilia, how did you guys
find me before I woke up?
Well, we discovered
you passed out
in the third floor archive.
[SUBARU]
The third floor archive?
[gasps]
After that, we carried you
from there to the green room.
So likely the archive,
or something within it,
was in some way responsible.
Well, that place is an archive
full of books of the dead,
after all.
Did you say
books of the dead?
That sounds like
something that would get
a teenage boy's heart racing.
The books of the dead
allow the one reading
to experience
the memories
of those lives vicariously.
Not that I would
want that experience.
So I was reading one
of them and then passed out?
Maybe that fried my brain
and made me lose my memories.
It's not impossible.
I could try to figure
it out in the archive.
Yeah!
Then after breakfast, we'll do
an on the spot investigation.
But at the same time,
we don't want a repeat
of what happened
to you yesterday.
So we'll do the investigating.
You stay here and rest
in the meantime.
I suppose.
Huh?
Damn it.
After all that,
I gave in to peer pressure.
Do I not even get a vote?
Status open!
No dice.
If this is a parallel world,
I was looking forward to
at least having magic, but--
You've permanently lost
your ability to ever use it.
You used too much beginner
magic you were told not to use
and broke your gate
beyond repair, I suppose.
What loser breaks their gate
with beginner stuff?
OK, then how about this?
[whip crack, groans]
Ow!
Isn't this the kind of thing
where muscle memory
should take over?
I should have at least
kept a diary of everything
I've done for a time like this.
I'm so useless now.
It'll be OK.
This is going to work.
In this world,
even I should be--
uh, whoops.
It's not this way.
Hmm?
Whoa!
What's with this staircase?
It looks like it
goes on forever.
[gasps]
[yells]
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
[thud, crunch]
[EMILIA]
Subaru, are you all right?
Emilia?
How--
[EMILIA]
Oh, what a relief.
I was really worried about you.
[BEATRICE] Emilia,
you need to be firmer with him
or he won't feel bad
about what he's done.
Yeah, you're right.
Like Beatrice said,
you've been naughty.
She panicked when we
couldn't find you anywhere,
and when we did find
you on the ground,
she almost started crying.
Huh? Hey!
You don't need to share
every little detail about that
with him, I suppose.
Huh?
Is this a dream?
[SUBARU]
Huh? What?
Wait, so you mean I passed
out in the archive again?
Again?
No, but you guys all stopped
me from going back the time
after that, so I didn't.
Stopped you?
I'm getting the feeling
we're talking about
two different things here.
Subaru, I want you to try
explaining to Betty in detail
exactly how you got here,
I suppose.
OK.
Well, like I said before,
when I woke up,
I discovered that
my memories had vanished.
- All of my memories--
- Wait, wait, wait, wait--
--since I was
summoned to this world.
Memories?
What's this about
your memories?
[SUBARU]
Huh?
Hold on.
That's what trips you up?
I mean, I already
told you two about--
uh.
I've definitely had this
conversation before.
Was that a prophetic dream?
Subaru?
I need you guys to stay
calm and hear me out.
See, I had a proph--
Huh?
I know what I'm about
to say might be hard
for you to believe,
but it seems like
I've lost my memory,
so that sucks.
[clap]
There.
All cheered up.
Things are far worse
for you than me
at the moment,
so I shouldn't be making
such unhappy faces.
[BEATRICE]
I can't believe this!
As per usual, you are such
a troublesome contractor,
I suppose.
This utterly
burdensome situation
had better not happen again,
or I will lose my patience--
No one seemed to know
about this in my dream either.
I didn't--
the Subaru Natsuki
they know didn't tell them
about this power.
But why, though?
What the hell were you
thinking, Subaru Natsuki?
What kind of stupid
joke is this, Barusu?
[SHAULA]
Hiya, Master.
I'm Shaula, AKA
your most beloved pupil,
and I'm also Keeper
of the Pleiades Watchtower.
[MEILI]
I swear.
Wow, what a guy.
You must really love
being a problem, huh?
My friend, I think he needs
a little time right now.
Is that all right?
[RAM]
I'm begging you.
Tell me everything.
[SUBARU]
This is all disturbingly
identical to my dream.
If there's one single problem--
OK, Subaru.
Stay and rest, all right?
[SUBARU]
It's not what they all do,
but what I decide
to do differently.
Master, your face is
looking super scary!
If something's troubling you,
you can always talk to me.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
What'd you do that for,
brat number two?
Well, I don't want
Emilia and Beatrice
getting mad at me for not
keeping you on a leash, 'k?
[growls]
Man, you piss me off!
Master, you've got
to say something to her.
Huh?
Nice save.
- Thanks, Meili.
- [groans]
It's probably sort of weird
to be thanking an assassin.
Master, you jerk!
[muffled sobbing]
You really don't
remember anything at all,
do you, Subaru?
[SUBARU]
Unfortunately, no.
Did I, like, make some
important promise or something?
If I did, how the hell
could yesterday's me
have been careless
enough to get himself
into this whole mess, huh?
Heh.
Yeah, yesterday's you
was indeed careless.
I fully agree with you there.
[SUBARU]
Right then.
I just need to find out why
I woke up from the dream
and what happened
after this point.
It goes on forever.
[gasps]
There's no point in fearing a
future that isn't set in stone.
That's it.
I'll tell them about
my prophetic dream.
If I can figure out
exactly how it works,
I know it'll be
a powerful asset.
That's why--
[MEILI]
I'm worried about keeping
Natsuki with us
any longer.
Isn't it too dangerous?
[RAM] I'm assuming you aren't
concerned about Barusu's safety
so much as you're
concerned that he'll
slow us down in this state?
If so, I agree.
[EMILIA] Ram,
even you're talking
about Subaru that way now?
[RAM] I was only stating
the objective truth.
[JULIUS]
Miss Emilia,
they're simply thinking about
the success of the mission
and pointing out that there
are too many uncertainties
involved in relying
on him right now.
[BEATRICE]
When you put it like that,
it sounds like you agree
with that spirit, I suppose.
[JULIUS]
Well, that's--
I had to hear all that right
after I decided to tell them?
Damn it!
[panting]
The way they're
talking about me,
I don't know if they'd even
believe me about the dream.
[yells]
[crunch]
[yelling]
[MEILI] I'm worried about
keeping Natsuki with us
any longer.
Isn't it too dangerous?
[RAM]
I agree.
[EMILIA] You're talking
about Subaru that way?
[JULIUS] Too many uncertainties
involved in relying on him.
[EMILIA] Our memories are what
make us everything we are.
You're still Subaru, after all.
[SUBARU]
Really?
[crunch]
Who do you think you are?
[gasps]
[yelling]
[coughing]
[EMILIA]
Subaru, what's wrong?
Take it easy.
[screams]
[BEATRICE] Subaru,
calm down, I suppose.
Beatrice!
Ah!
[screaming]
[sobbing]
[laughing]
[REID]
Hey, kid.
What in the hell do you
think you're doing up here
so early in the morning, huh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Come on, bro.
You're not crying, are ya?
Did you get in a fight with
your buddies downstairs
or something, kid?
You crying because you
lost an argument or what?
[gasps]
[groaning]
[REID] The hell makes
you think you can
just bring your problems here?
And your tiny little legs
ran up to me on top of it.
What kind of joke is that, huh?
You're the one who chose
the people you're stuck
hanging out with in here.
Or is it that you
just got a death wish?
Beat it, loser.
[screams]
[crunching]
[sobbing]
No.
It hurts.
It hurts so much.
[sobbing]
It was only a few hours ago
I was with my dad and my mom,
and then--
[MOM]
Take care of yourself.
[SUBARU] I didn't feel
like washing the mug,
so I left without
saying a word to my mom.
I should have told her
that I'd be back soon.
I'm such a damn screwup.
I never got to repay
her for everything.
Couldn't even do some dishes.
I'll die without--
[laughter]
Don't laugh.
Stop laughing at me.
Don't you dare laugh at me!
[laughter]
Don't laugh!
Stop it!
I'm gonna die, but I won't--
I won't let myself
be killed by you!
You can't!
I refuse to let
you take my life!
I'm too tired.
No, I'm gonna die.
No way!
I'm not dying!
I'm dead!
I'm so dead!
I'll die!
I'll come back here,
but I will never let you--
I love you.
[gasps]
No, stop.
[screaming]
Just hurry and kill me already.
[EMILIA]
Subaru!
[sobbing weakly]
[EMILIA]
Subaru?
[groaning softly]
Rem deserves much better.
Subaru, just stay in here
and relax, all right?
Betty will find a way
to remedy this, I suppose.
I won't sit by and allow you
to just cower here all alone.
[footsteps]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
It's happened twice.
I've died twice now.
The moment I died after that
fall, I went back to that room
and it repeated again,
that same span of time.
It's no prophetic dream.
It's Return by Death.
So I'll just get
someone to kill me.
♪ ♪
[gasps]
Master.
WHO ARE YOU?